♪I defy heaven, fate,
and so-called immortality♪
♪At last you say
we've been apart too long♪
♪Unwilling, unyielding, I won't let go♪
♪With you, even a dried sea
learns to embrace a stream♪
♪If heaven divides us, I'll reunite us,
with love as our vessel♪
♪If it forbids it, I'll shatter
the absurd Heavenly Dao♪
♪Even if countless stars
turn into my foes♪
♪To grow old with you, we burn
through the end of the long night♪
=Rise Again=
=Episode 12=
You only dare to throw hidden weapons,
but not to face me in person?
My lady heard you're unbeatable, Mr. Su.
She sent me
to invite you for a chat.
And if I say no?
That's fine.
I happen to know
where Miss Lin Ningxue is.
Don't blame me
if something happens to her.
This is...
A dart from the Shan family.
Shan Yingying,
what are you up to this time?
Mr. Gu.
He's here.
Leave.
Mr. Gu, my reward...
Out.
Bring him in.
Mr. Gu.
Knew it was you all along.
Don't use the martial hall's darts.
What's going on between
you and Jiang Yao?
Ningxue's furious.
Isn't it obvious?
It's a setup by Gu Yuanbing.
He lured me there on purpose.
Nothing happened
between me and her.
You expect me to believe that?
You've been hiding right under my nose.
You've got an agenda
by getting close to Ningxue.
That's between me and her.
I'll explain it myself.
If there's nothing else,
I'm leaving.
I didn't say you could leave.
Make your move.
Enough?
I'm just getting started.
Too rush.
Weak stance.
You're wide open.
Cut the crap!
Let me go. That's cheating.
I'm not even trying.
You've got no balance.
Who's there?
(Shan Guohao, Shan Family Head)
Coming to challenge the Shan family?
Think we've got no one left?
Dad, he's my friend,
not here to challenge us.
Why didn't you say so?
I almost hurt him.
Dad, you okay?
I'm fine.
This kid is impressive.
Has he reached Mystic-level too?
Mr. Shan.
To think someone so young
could fight me to a draw.
Looks like Fan City's got
some real talents lately.
Dad,
he's from our martial hall.
What?
How come I didn't know
we had someone this good?
What's your name?
Su Wubing!
(Head Disciple, Shan Martial Hall)
Mr. Shan, long time no see.
For real?
Absolutely.
Everyone in Fan City knows
the Lin and Shan families are close.
Shan Yingying must've challenged him
to avenge Lin Ningxue.
This is our chance.
When he crashed the wedding,
the Shan family was in on it too..
Still haven't settled that score.
Mr. Gu.
Then I'll...
Get ready.
After tonight, you'll be head
of the Shan family.
Thank you, Mr. Gu.
Tch. Traitor.
Mr. Shan, know when to back down.
The Shan family can't hold
on much longer.
If you side with Mr. Gu,
life will be much better.
Enough talk.
Finish him.
Got it.
You think a traitor like him?
Today I'll enforce family law,
and expel him from the sect.
Then I'll deal with you.
Dad!
How did he get this strong?
Guards!
I hear you're early Mystic-level.
Take this.
No one can beat you tonight.
This... this is...?
Our Gu family's latest product.
Only one of its kind.
Take it, and for a short time,
your power will increase tenfold.
Such a miracle drug?
But it will cost you
twenty years of your life.
What?
Twenty years?
So what?
Twenty years
for the Shan family head position.
Worth it.
Smart choice.
Help me up.
Shameless.
Don't!
That traitor's already
at peak Mystic-level.
Su Wubing, you should go.
I'll handle this.
None of you are leaving.
Today, you all die here.
♪I defy heaven, fate,
and so-called immortality♪
♪At last you say
we've been apart too long♪
♪Unwilling, unyielding, I won't let go♪
♪With you, even a dried sea
learns to embrace a stream♪
♪If heaven divides us, I'll reunite us,
with love as our vessel♪
♪If it forbids it, I'll shatter
the absurd Heavenly Dao♪
♪Even if countless stars
turn into my foes♪
♪To grow old with you, we burn
through the end of the long night♪